████████████████████████████████████████
█                  █████████████████████
█  ████  █    █ ███   ██     ██       ██
█ █    █ █    █   █ ████ █████████ █████
█ █      █    █   █ ████ █████████ █████
█  ████  ██████   █ ████    ██████ █████
█      █ █    █   █ ████ █████████ █████
█ █    █ █    █   █ ████ █████████ █████
█  ████  █    █ ███   ██ █████████ █████
█                  █████████████████████
████████████████████████████████████████
A Puzzle Game By Alex Marcolina
Based off the Flash Game
An Angel Production
Builderboy2005@yahoo.com

Contents:
I:------Introduction
II:-----Installation
III:----Gameplay
IV:-----Level Editor
V:------Known Bugs
VI:-----Conclusion

████████████████
█I)Introduction█
████████████████

	Is the ceiling the floor?  Is the floor the ceiling?  SHIFT is a unique puzzle platformer
based off the Flash Game.  In SHIFT, there is no such thing as solid ground, what you may be standing
ontop of one second, becomes empty space when you SHIFT.  With this original concept, 10 built in
Levels to start, and a Powerful Level Editor, SHIFT is the ultimate Puzzle Platform Game.

████████████████
█II)Instalation█
████████████████
	
	To Install Shift, send the program SHIFT, Pic1, and xLib to your Calculator.  Make sure you
Install xLib before playing, or the game will not work.  Also note that this game is NOT MirageOS
compatible, so you will need to have it unarchived and run it from the home screen.

	If you are having trouble sending the files to your calculator, try sending the group file
(which is identical) and ungrouping it on-calc.  If that doesn't work, you can always email me at
Builderboy2005@yahoo.com for tech support :)

██████████████
█III)Gameplay█
██████████████

	When you first run SHIFT, you should be greeted by the Production Logo, and then proceed to the main
menu.  Use the arrow keys to scroll up and down to select 1 of the 3 options: Play, Custom, or Exit

:Play brings you to the first Level, or if you have saved data, lets you select a Level you have already beaten.

:Custom will prompt you to Input the name of a Level you have created with the Level editor.

:Exit exits the program :P

While playing the game, the controls are as follows:

[Left/right] - Moves your character Left and Right
[Up] --------- Jump.  Note that you can press [Up] and [Left]or[Right] to jump diagonaly
[ALPHA] ------ Shift.  Makes the ground empty space and visa-versa.  Flips the world upside-down!
[Clear] ------ Access the ingame Menu, where you can Restart, go back to the Main Menu, or Return to your game

██████████████████
█IV) Level Editor█
██████████████████

NOTE: The Level Editor is NOT made with User friendliness in Mind.  It is only intended for creating
Levels for SHIFT.

The first Menu will ask if you want to create a new Level or Load an Old one.  If you choose New, you will
go directly to the Edit Menu.  If you choose Load, you will be prompted for the List the the Level resides
in.

The Edit Menu have several functions:
Block:
Doors:
Start:
Save:
Exit:

Block: Allows you to edit the tiles of the map directly.  Use the numberpad to select the tile to place down.
0:Blank
1:Filled
2:Spikes
3:Spikes (filled)
4:Key
5:Key    (filled)
6:Door
7:Door	 (filled)

The filled tiles are tiles that are inverted and become regular only when you shift.  Note that they are also
upside-down.

Doors: Selects which blocks move when you acquire keys.  This Action must be selected in order to save your level!
When you select it, it will highlight each key that has been placed on the screen, and you must select the block
that will move when that key has been selected.  Once you select the block, press the direction on the arrow keys
you wish the block to slide when activated (blocks slide 2 spaces).  Theh bloacks you can select are regular filled blocks,
rightside up doors, and rightside up spikes.

Start: Select the Starting Space for your character.  This Action must be selected in order to save your level!

Save: Saves your level to L1.  Will only save if both the action Doors and Start have been defined.  A * will appear
next to the actions if you need to run them.

Exit: Exit without saving.


NOTE: That the level editor is made without any checks, so it is entirely possible to create a level that causes the
Shift game to glitch.  The Level Editor is only meant for people who have played the game, have a good understanding of
how it works, and know what they want to do.

██████████████
█V)Known Bugs█
██████████████

There are no Known bugs with the Level Editor or any of the 10 default levels, but if you do find any
be sure to report them to Builderboy2005@yahoo.com

Again, Bad levels made by the level editor have the potential to break the game, and don't count as bugs :)

███████████████
█VI)Conclusion█
███████████████

	Thank you for downloading my game :) I hope you enjoy it.  If you feel you have made a nice and puzzling level
with the Level Editor, please contact me and it might be added in the new version! As this version is slightly small, due to the rushed natue of production.

If you come across any problems or have anything to say, again, please contact me!  Thanks for playing my game!

(The timer is a Lie!)

Alex Marcolina
Angel Productions
Builderboy2005@yAahoo.com